# bibo **Amakiri**

6 Oxford Avenue, Egbelu Ozodo Port Harcourt, Nigeria

📞 +2348038747806 | 附 officialsoibibo@gmail.com | in Soibibo Amakiri | 🧓 @soibiboamakiri | ይ +2347065301316







# Summary

Soibibo Amakiri is a proficient, experienced and results-oriented Frontend Developer, having 3+ years of experience. Offering a strong attention to detail and accuracy, excellent problem-solving skills, and the important ability to work in fastpaced team environment. I am the reliable individual with a determination to meet and exceed all assigned results.

### Technical Skills

**Strongest Areas** Web Development, Webhosting, Ui Designs, Graphics, Logo Designs, Branding

Programming Languages HTML5, CSS3, PHP, JavaScript, Sass,

Frameworks / Libraries Bootstrap, React, Node.js, jQuery, Wordpress, Codeigniter, Laravel, Composer

**Database** MySQL, PHPMyAdmin

**Others** Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Figma, Adobe XD, Corel Draw, Ms Word, Powerpoint,

## Education

Goldson's Computer

Eagle junction, Rumuolumeni Port Harcourt, Nigeria

ADV. DIPLOMA IN COMPUTER TRAINING

January 2015 - July 2015

Ignatius Ajuru University of Education

Rumuolumeni Port Harcourt, Nigeria

BSC IN COMPUTER SCIENCE (CSC) · SECOND CLASS (LOWER DIVISION) September 2016 - March 2021

Work Experience

# Stormcell Integrated Services Limited

Remote

Github

Github

June 2019 - July. 2022

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

· Play a vital role as Frontend lead Developer.

• Tasked to come up with creative Ui/ux designs for various projects.

• Tasked to comeup with graphics design concept and branding.

#### Community Secondary School, Bayelsa State Nigeria, NYSC

Agudama Epie, Yenegoa Bayelsa, Nigeria

Computer Science Teacher

November 2021 - November 2022

Managed over 300 students at a time to ensure effective learning and appropriate behaviour

Motivated the students to move past their current academic performance, and successfully increased the pass rate on standardized test to 70% for juniors and 85% for seniors

# **Projects**

FRONTEND UI DESIGNER

**Schchat** HTML, CSS, Bootstrap

• Developed a fully responsive webpage on schchat.com

• Developed a responsive Login and Register webpage

- · Implemented a User friendly dashboard on schchat.com
- · Visit Link: https://schchat.com

**Partste** Wordpress

**ECOMMERCE WEBSITE** 

• Developed a fully responsive ecommerce system using wordpress framework.

- Integrated Woocommerce to make the ecommerce system operational.
- Integrated a payment gateway using Paystack to enable product purchase.

Visit Link: <a href="https://partste.ng">https://partste.ng</a>

Credib **Figma** Github **UI/UX DESIGNER** 

- · Design a User friendly mobile interface.
- Design a User friendly webpages.
- Visit Link: https://credib.io

#### Vocational Jobs

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

# **Stormcell Integrated Services Limited**

Remote

• Play a vital role as Frontend lead Developer.

• Tasked to come up with some creative Ui designs for various projects.

Tasked to comeup with graphics designs concept and branding.

# Interests

- Reading.
- · Communication.
- · Travelling.
- · Team player.
- Video game. Football.

June 2019 - July 2022